TOM YOUNG

AKA Yang Tianji $\diamond +65$ 86944289 \diamond Singapore

Email | Twitter | Homepage | Google Scholar | Github

HIGHLIGHT

6 years of experience in NLP and deep learning; total No. citations >4000.

PhD of Computer Science Nanyang Technological University, Singapore

Bachelor of Engineering Beijing Institute of Technology, Beijing

Most recent work is on improving large masked language models.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Fellow National University of Singapore	Sep. 2022 - now
Research intern Continental Inc., Singapore	Apr. 2019 - Oct. 2019
Research intern Baidu Inc., Beijing	Mar. 2018 - Jun. 2018
Research assistent Tsinghua University, Beijing	Aug. 2017 - Feb. 2018
EDUCATION	

Jul 2018 - Aug 2022

Sep 2014 - Jun 2018

RESEARCH INTEREST

Pushing forward the capabilities of foundational models, such as long-range understanding, reasoning and multi-modality.

PUBLICATIONS

- On the Inconsistencies of Conditionals Learned by Masked Language Models, **Tom Young**, Yang You, arXiv preprint arXiv:2301.00068
- Fusing Task-oriented and Open-domain Dialogues in Conversational Agents, **Tom Young**, F Xing, V Pandelea, J Ni, E Cambria, AAAI 2022
- Recent Trends in Deep Learning Based Natural Language Processing, Tom Young, D Hazarika, S Poria, and E Cambria, IEEE Computational Intelligence Magazine 2018
- Augmenting End-to-End Dialogue Systems with Commonsense Knowledge, Tom Young, E Cambria, I Chaturvedi,
 H Zhou, S Biswas, M Huang, AAAI 2018
- Dialogue Systems with Audio Context, Tom Young, V Pandelea, S Poria, E Cambria, Neurocomputing 2020
- HiTKG: Towards Goal-oriented Conversations via Multi-hierarchy Learning, J Ni, V Pandelea, **Tom Young**, H Zhou, E Cambria, AAAI 2022
- Toward Hardware-aware Deep Learning Based Dialogue Systems, V Pandelea, E Ragusa, **Tom Young**, P Gastaldo, E Cambria, Neural Computing and Applications 2021
- Recent Advances in Deep Learning Based Dialogue Systems: A Systematic Survey, J Ni, **Tom Young**, V Pandelea, F Xue, V Adiga, E Cambria, Artificial intelligence review 2023
- Commonsense Knowledge Aware Conversation Generation with Graph Attention, H Zhou, Tom Young, M Huang, H Zhao, J Xu, and X Zhu, IJCAI 2018

(more on next page)

PROFESSIONAL SERVICES & TEACHING

Journal reviewer Knowledge-Based Systems, Cognitive Computation,

IEEE Transactions on Affective Computing, Artificial Intelligence Review

Conference reviewer ACL 2020, ACL 2021, AAAI 2023, AAAI 2024

Teaching NTU-CE1003: Intro to Computation Thinking

NTU-CZ2004: Human Computer Interaction

NUS-CS5260: Neural Networks and Deep Learning II

AWARDS & RESEARCH IMPACT

• 2018 IJCAI Distinguished Paper Award

• 2021 IEEE CIM Outstanding Paper Award

• Google Scholar Citations: 4000+